C. Tavis Post

Fullstack developer

Seattle, WA

206.992.1518

ctavispost@gmail.com
Github
LinkedIn

ctavispost.com

Profile

I am an inclusive, thoughtful fullstack developer with past experience in UX and writing consultancy. I work across roles with broad, practical empathy and a deep curiosity. Whether designing or building an app, I create open and inclusive interactions based on research, dialogue, and data.

Experience

UX engineer, CTPost Design

March 2018 - present

- Design and refine sites like <u>findthemasks</u>, serving over 30,000 people per day and providing key information to a network of international organizations
- Create inclusive content and interactions to inform, guide, and delight customers and users.

Writing consultant, ELP Forensic Social Work

January 2012 - May 2018

- Crafted clear and impactful narratives from primary documents and stakeholder interviews (up to 300 pages) to support findings in as little as 48 hours.
- Wrote plans (20–48 pages) for treatment and family reunification in complex court cases 12 to 24 times a year.

Fourth manager, QFC

October 2008 - March 2018

- Trained and mentored diverse staff of 64 people.
- Consulted customers, employees, data, and surveys to form strategies to increase profit by 4% year over year and increase customer satisfaction by 20%.

Education

General Assembly SEI

• Fullstack development.

University of Washington

1999–2006

• Philosophy, Japanese.

Skills

object oriented programming, prototyping, wireframes, flows, user testing, surveys, interviews, personas, mockups, storyboards, research, sketching, illustration, storytelling, user centered design

Tools

HTML5, CSS3, JavaScript, jQuery, React, Python, Bootstrap, Jekyll, Git, Trello, Heroku, Ruby, Rails, WordPress, pencil & paper

Projects

findthemasks.com

find where and how to donate PPE

moodpatch

mood tracking fullstack web app

the green room

album search server rendered app